crisiseducation.com 2018-03-02

# Privacy Policy – Self-Reliance Association

Privacy is our business – we live and die by it. And we know that it is critically important to our customers as well. We are constantly studying new developments, laws and methods of protecting your privacy.

We don’t even allow our employees to see our customer information, and our system does not record your IP address.

HERE’S THE BOTTOM LINE: WE WILL NOT EVER GIVE, SELL, LOSE, MISPLACE OR RENT YOUR INFORMATION TO ANYONE – EVER.

Now for the legalese:

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.  
Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘do we use cookies?’ section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

What do we use your information for?

The information we collect from you may be used to process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or access your personal information.

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely, PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities or No one at Freedom Writer’s Publishing has access to credit card information. All credit card information is encrypted and sent directly to the card processor, and is never held on our servers..  
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Do we use cookies?

Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information).

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links.

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.  
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

CAN-SPAM Compliance

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This policy was last modified on July 29, 2016.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

Freedom Writers Publishing  
PO Box 774000-358 1815 Central Park Dr.  
Steamboat Springs, CO 80477  
United States  
970-367-7624

Chris@SelfRely.com

Privacy Policy Customer Pledge  
We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the the following important privacy laws and initiatives:

  * Federal Trade Commission Fair
  * California Online Privacy Protection Act
  * Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act
  * Privacy Alliance
  * Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act

If at anytime you have a cause that needs to be disputed please fill out the Trust Guard Dispute Resolution form.

Respectfully,  
_Chris Peterson_ , President  
Freedom Writers Publishing
